

627 12 96 59



antoniomartinezfernandez17@g mail.com



Murcia, Murcia, España



<u>Gith</u>ub



Website

# **Idiomas**

# Spanish:

Native

#### English:

High level

# **Estudios**

#### **Degree in Computer Science**

Software Engineering Specialization Average grade: 7.2 Software Architecture with honors

### **Bachelor and High School**

Health sciences Bachelor Average grade: 8.1 Bilingual high school

#### **Otros**

- Own vehicle
- Type B Driving license

# **Antonio Martínez**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

# Sobre mí

I am 22 years old and currently reside in Murcia, with availability for remote work. I am passionate about software development. I have developed various applications such as Spotify Electron, an open-source, cross-platform music streaming application, programming challenges like Advent of Code, and B-Baka Bot, a Discord bot.

# Experiencia laboral

# **Backend developer Python at Bionet**

October 2023 - Present

Backend Developer responsible for implementing new features, troubleshooting issues, and promoting unit and integration testing methodologies in the embedde software for ROSITA2 and CTB bioreactors.

- Python and FastAPI
- Extensive integration and unit testing using PyTest.
- Data parallelism and asynchrony in high-performance tasks. Multithreading and asyncio.
- Communication between frontend and low-level electronic devices.
- Use of MySQL and SQLite databases.
- · Git, Bitbucket, Docker and Portainer
- Working with agile methodologies. Usage of Jira and Kanban.

# **Lead Developer at Spotify Electron**

May 2023 - Present

As the CEO and Lead Developer of an open-source cross-platform music streaming application, I have been at the forefront of replicating and enhancing Spotify's functionalities while incorporating unique user-requested features such as the ability to upload personal music

- Python + FastAPI + MongoDB for Backend.
- React + TypeScript for Frontend.
- AWS Lambda, S3 and Cloudfront for cloud services.
- Git, Github, Github Actions, Docker,
- Full test coverage with Pytest and Jest.

#### Backend developer PHP at ByProx

January 2021 - April 2021

I was in charge of the backend development of a travel application that managed the organization and navigation of points of interest in different regions and countries.

- Developed the logic for organizing points of interest using PHP.
- Data persistence using MySQL databases.